Finding Aid for Republican Party (Mich.). State Central Committee Records ca. 1958-1979
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Staff Files/Department Files
  - Research Division
    - People file circa 1962-1970
      - Towns, Fred B. (Box 29)
      - Tyson, Charles E. (Box 29)
      - Upton, David (Box 29)
      - Van Dam, Philip Michiel (Box 29)
      - VanderJagt, Guy, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Vanderlaan, Robert (Box 29)
      - Van Dusen, Richard C. (Box 29)
      - Van Peursem, George M., 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Van Til, Riemer (Box 29)
      - Varnum, Charles (Box 29)
      - Ver Duin, Claude (Box 29)
      - Volkema, Harold J. (Box 29)
      - Wahls, Myron (Box 29)
      - Waldron, Robert (Box 29)
      - Walker, Frank B. (Box 29)
      - Walker, Richard W. (Box 29)
      - Wallace, George (Box 29)
      - Warner, Dale (Box 29)
      - Warshawsky, Meyer (Box 29)
      - Washington, George (Box 29)
      - Weber, William V. (Box 29)
      - Welborn, John (Jack) (Box 29)
      - Westphal, Albert H. (Box 29)
      - White, Ink (Box 29)
      - Whittaker, Alfred H. (Box 29)
      - Widgery, Robin (Box 29)
      - Williams, Clara B. (Box 29)
      - Williams, Herbert (Box 29)
      - Woodman, Blair (Box 29)
      - Wurzel, Raymond (Box 29)
      - Yeager, Weldon O. (Box 29)
      - Young, Robert (Box 29)
      - Zaagman, Milton (Box 29)
      - Ziegler, Hal (Box 29)
      - Zollar, Charles O. (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous biographies
      - A-O, 14 folders (Box 29)
      - P-Z, 8 folders (Box 30)
      - District chairmen (Box 30)
      - Republican National Committee (Box 30)
      - Republican State Central Committee members 1969 (Box 30)
      - State Representative candidates (Box 30)
      - State Senate candidates (Box 30)
      - Task Force members (Box 30)
      - Unprocessed, 3 folders (Box 30)
  - Press Division
    - Press releases
      - Undated and 1963-1968 (Box 30)
      - 1969-1978 (Box 30)
  - Republican State Finance Committee
    - Dated files 1952-1962 (Box 31)
    - Dated files 1963-1969 (Box 32)
    - Dated files 1969-1978 (Box 33)
    - Topical files (not listed or alphabetized) (Box 33)
  - State Republican Organizations (Box 34)
    - Publications
      - Accent (Republican State Nationalities Council) (Box 35)
      - The Activist (Michigan Federation of College Republicans) (Box 35)
      - College Republican News (MSU College Republicans) (Box 35)
      - Detroit Young Republican News (Box 35)
      - Elephant's trumpet (Kalamazoo County Republican Committee) (Box 35)
      - Forecast (House Republican Program Section) (Box 35)
      - Michigan Republican Contributor News (Michigan Republican Finance Committee) (Box 35)
      - Republican Bulletin (Republican Women's Federation of Michigan) (Box 35)
      - Republican News and Views (Genesee County Republican Party) (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous Republican publications (Box 35)
    - Various Republican groups
      - Republican Agricultural Council circa 1965-1967 (Box 35)
      - Research Advisory Committee circa 1954-1969 (Box 35)
      - Republican Senior Citizens and Retirees Council (and senior citizens) circa 1964-1974 (Box 35)
      - Michigan Republican Servicemen's Council 1967-1970 (Box 35)
      - Republican War Veterans of Michigan 1944-1968 (Arthur Hagen/Herman Luhrs files) (Box 35)
    - Young Republicans (also other Republican youth organizations/youth issues) (Box 36)
      - General and unprocessed (Box 36)
      - Michigan Federation of Young Republicans (Box 37)
      - Michigan Teen-age Republicans (TARS) (Box 37)
      - Michigan Federation of College Republicans (Box 37)
      - Local Young Republican organizations (Box 37)
      - Wolverine Boys State 1975-1977 (Box 37)
      - Youth Council (Richard Posthumus files) (Box 37)
    - Nationalities/minorities
      - Republican State Nationality Council (Box 38)
      - Nationalities (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
      - National Black Republican Council (Box 38)
      - Irish-American Republican Club (Box 38)
      - National Hispanic Assembly (Box 38)
    - Women
      - Republican women's organizations (individual files not listed) (Box 38)
      - Republican women's organizations (individual files not listed) (Box 39)
- Topical Files
  The Topical Files is a large series, approximately 11 linear feet in size, and drawn from different and miscellaneous sources. The origin of the materials is not clear though some of it undoubtedly could be associated with the research subseries described Staff Files/Department Files, or with the subject files maintained by the chair of the SCC. Because of this uncertainty, the files were drawn together and alphabetized. Significant portions of this series detail Republican party meetings and conferences.
  - Abortion 1967-1971 (Box 39)
  - Absentee ballot 1974, 1976 (Box 39)
  - Absentee voting 1972 (Box 39)
  - Advertising, (Ann Arbor) 1970 (Box 39)
  - Agnew, Spiro T. 1970-1972 (Box 39)
  - Agriculture 1963-1966 (Box 39)
  - Aid to dependent children of the unemployed 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Aid to dependent children of the unemployed, (Fedewa thesis) 1965 (Box 39)
  - American Airlines political contributions 1977 (Box 39)
  - American Council of Young Political Leaders 1976-1978 (Box 39)
  - Area Redevelopment Administration 1963 (Box 39)
  - Audio-visual presentations: Crossroads of Decision, Mission '70, Call for Action, Republicans vs. Democrats 1962-1963 (Box 40)
  - Automotive News Services 1972-1975 (Box 40)
  - Auxiliary groups 1969-1970 (Box 40)
  - Ballot issue 1972-1976 (Box 40)
  - Bicentennial Committee 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Billboards 1970 (outdoor advertising) (Box 40)
  - Board of Canvassers 1964 (Box 40)
  - Budget 1959-1970 (state) (Box 40)
  - Bussing 1971 (Box 40)
  - Calendars for Republican Party Workers 1964-1978 (scattered) (Box 40)
  - Campaign finance study undated (Box 40)
  - Campaign finance reform, (federal) 1972-1974 (Box 40)
  - Campaign finance reform, (state) 1973-1974 (Box 40)
  - Campaign Managers seminar 1970 (Box 40)
  - Campaign organization, (guidelines, etc.) 1958, undated (Box 40)
  - Campaign Seminar for chairmen and vice-chairmen 1973-1974 (Box 40)
  - Candidates School 1978, undated, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Citizens Conference on State Legislature 1973 (Michigan Legislative-News Media Conference) (Box 40)
  - Civil rights
    - General 1958-1965, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Coordinating Council on Civil Rights 1958-1960 (Box 40)
    - Michigan Commission on Civil Rights 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 40)
    - Opening housing 1960-1961
  - Civil service 1962 (Box 40)
  - Coffee prices 1964 (Box 40)
  - Committee assignments on RSCC 1977 (Box 40)
  - Common Cause 1974 (Box 40)
  - CompuGraphics 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Conferences, fund raising events, meetings, etc.
    - 1956-1964 (Box 40)
    - 1965-1976 (Box 41)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 42)
  - Congress, Correspondence with members of 1970, 1973 (Box 42)
  - Conservatives 1964-1968 (Box 42)
    (district committees, United Republicans of Michigan, and conservative clubs)
  - Constitutional Convention 1961-1963, 1 folders; 1 volumes (Box 42)
  - Convention procedures 1973-1974 (delegate selection, etc.) (Box 43)
  - County Board of Supervisors 1968 (Box 43)
  - County Committee correspondence 1964 (Box 43)
  - County Committee Officers 1959-1960, 1968, 2 folders (Box 43)
  - County Republican executive committees 1966, 1972-1974, 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Couples clubs 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Damman, James 1974-1978, 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Democratic State Central Committee 1965-1971 (Box 43)
  - Detroit Economic Club 1975-1979 (Box 43)
  - Detroit Great Decisions Program 1962 (Box 43)
  - Direct mail program 1977-1978 (Box 43)
  - District committees, 6 folders (Box 43)
  - Drop-outs from school 1963-1964 (Box 43)
  - Durant, Richard (and 14th Republican District) 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Economy (state) 1948-1962, 5 folders (Box 43)
  - Economy (state) 1963 (Box 43)
  - Economy (state) 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Education 1972-1975 (Box 43)
  - Education 1977 (Box 43)
  - Education (lower) 1961-1967 (Box 43)
  - Education reform 1969-1970 (Box 43)
  - Election bills 1966-1967 (Box 44)
  - Election Data Processing Advisory Committee and related 1966-1970 (Box 44)
    (ca. 7 lin. in.; not further described)
  - Election irregularities, fraud, and recount, 6 folders (Box 44)
  - Election Law Alert (Box 44)
  - Election Law Committee 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Election law reform 1973 (Box 44)
  - Election Laws, 4 folders (Box 45)
  - Election reform (national) 1968-1970 (Box 45)
  - Employment 1970 (Box 45)
  - Executive office correspondence 1970 (Box 45)
  - Fair (Michigan State Fair) booths 1967-1977 (Box 45)
  - Farmers Action Committee (Box 45)
  - Financial statements 1967 (Box 45)
  - Goettler Associates (Box 45)
  - Gunaca (John) extradition case 1954-1959 (Box 45)
  - Hispanic Republican Day 1977 (Box 45)
  - History of Party (Box 45)
  - Housing and Urban Development (Dept. of) 1969-1970 (Box 45)
  - Inaugurals (state and national) 1969-1975 (Box 45)
  - Institute in Practical Partisan Politics 1959 (Box 45)
  - Inter-office memos 1963-1964 (Box 45)
  - Jaycees 1973-1974 (Box 45)
  - John Birch Society 1962, 1966, 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Key Republican Club 1970 (Box 45)
  - Labor (Republican accomplishments) 1958-1966 (Box 45)
  - Legislative Dinner 1970-1975 (Box 45)
  - Liberty Lobby 1966 (Box 45)
  - Life Underwriter Political Action Committee 1975 (Box 45)
  - Lincoln Day Dinners 1960-1972, 11 folders (Box 45)
  - Lincoln Day Dinners 1973-1978, 5 folders (Box 46)
  - Mackinac Bridge 1963-1966 (Box 46)
  - Mackinac Republican Leadership Conference 1963-1969 (Box 46)
  - Mandate (young Republican organization) 1971 (Box 46)
  - Manuals (leader's, leadership, county chairman's), 3 folders (Box 46)
  - Market Opinion Research 1973-1976, 4 folders; 4 volumes (Box 46)
  - Martin Luther King Day 1978 (Box 46)
  - Medicare circa 1962 (Box 46)
  - Membership program (Julie Abraham) 1973 (Box 46)
  - Mental health circa 1958-1964 (Box 46)
  - Metropolitan Action Center 1967-1968 (Box 46)
  - Michigan Center for Education in Politics 1964-1965 (Box 46)
  - Michigan Federation of Young Republicans (Box 46)
  - Michigan Republican 300 Club 1969 (Box 46)
  - Michigan State Legislature 1967-1968 (Box 46)
  - Michigan State Legislature. House of Representatives
    - 1966-1968 (Box 46)
    - 1973 (Box 46)
    - House bills (Box 46)
  - Michigan State Legislature. Senate
    - 1961-1962 (Box 46)
    - 1970 (Box 46)
    - Senate bills (Box 46)
    - Senate Republican Information Office 1975-1976 (Box 46)
  - Midwest and Rocky Mountain Republican State Chairmen's Association 1959-1961 (Box 46)
  - Midwest State Chairmen's Association 1975-1977 (Box 46)
  - Midwest Region Republican Conference 1969 (Box 46)
  - Minorities 1962-1973 (Box 46)
  - Mission: Involvement 1967-1968 (Box 47)
  - Mission 70s 1970 (Box 47)
    (Manual and workbook)
  - National Conference of Republican State Chairmen 1977 (Box 47)
  - National Governors' Conference 1977 (Box 47)
  - Neighbor to Neighbor program (meeting guide) (Box 47)
  - Nelson, Earl 1978 (Box 47)
    (acceptance of loan)
  - Nixon, Richard M. 1968-1970 (Box 47)
  - November Three-for-all (Box 47)
  - Operation Coffee Cup 1962-1964 (Box 47)
  - Operation Recruit 1964 (Box 47)
  - Opportunities Unlimited 1967 (Box 47)
  - Organization (club organization manuals, worker recruitment manuals, other how-to-organize materials), 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Parochiaid 1968-1970 (Box 47)
  - Party reform 1973 (Box 47)
  - Party structure legislation 1974-1975 (Box 47)
  - Party unity 1975 (Box 47)
  - Personnel policies (Box 47)
  - Plain talk 1965-1968 (Box 47)
  - Politicon 1973-1975 (Box 47)
  - Poll data 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Poverty, war on 1966 (Box 48)
  - President Ford Committee 1976-1977 (Box 48)
  - Press (letters to editor from William McLaughlin) 1971 (Box 48)
  - Primary election data, 1956 through 1962 (Box 48)
  - Regional Leadership Seminars 1975, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Republican Brotherhood Foundation 1971 (Box 48)
  - Republican Campaign Institute 1977, 5 folders (Box 48)
  - Republican Day 1977 (Box 48)
  - Republican Governors' Association 1973-1974 (Box 48)
  - Republican Legislative Handbook 1960 (Box 48)
  - Republican National Committee 1961-1965, 4 folders (Box 48)
  - Republican Party: organization, history, philosophy (Box 48)
  - Republican State Central Committee mailings (Box 48)
  - Republican State Central Committees (relations with other chairmen) (Box 48)
  - Republican Revision and Reorganization Committee 1973 (Box 48)
  - Revitalize the State Republican Party Committee 1975 (Box 48)
  - Ripon Society 1971-1977 (Box 48)
  - Romney, George (about)
    - General (Box 48)
    - Criticisms (Box 48)
  - Romney Girls 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Romney Volunteers 1962-1963 (Box 48)
  - Rosters (district and county) (Box 48)
  - Safety construction codes 1961 (Box 48)
  - Second Congressional District Republican Committee (Box 48)
  - Selective Service 1966 (Box 48)
  - Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore 1965-1966 (Box 48)
  - Supreme Court Candidate Selection Committee 1977-1978 (Box 48)
  - Swing districts 1964-1966 (Box 48)
  - Task Forces (Box 49)
    (.6 lin. ft.; contents not further described)
  - Taxation crises 1956-1958 (Box 49)
  - Taxation crises 1959-1960, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Taxation crises 1961-1962 (Box 49)
  - Taxes - Federal tax sharing 1965-1967 (Box 49)
  - Telephone campaign material 1974 (Box 49)
  - Telephone Center. Chairman's notebook 1974 (Box 49)
  - Telephone centers (and computer services) 1975-1978 (Box 49)
  - Unemployment compensation 1958-1962 (Box 49)
  - United Republican Fund circa 1967-1970 (Box 49)
  - United Republicans of Michigan (Box 49)
  - United States Labor Party 1976 (Box 49)
  - Upper Peninsula 1963-1965 (Box 49)
  - Veterans 1962-1968 (Box 49)
  - VIP (Victory Information Program) - Leader's Guide and miscellaneous 1962-1964 (Box 49)
  - VIP (Victory Information Program) - directory materials 1967 (Box 49)
  - Vietnam 1966 (Box 49)
  - Vignette (on ballot) - Lincoln and Romney 1966 (Box 49)
  - VIM 1967 (Box 50)
    (newsletter prepared by the Research Division of the Republican State Central Committee)
  - Volunteers: precinct delegates 1978 (Box 50)
  - Voter I.D. materials (Box 50)
  - Voter registration drive, 4 folders (Box 50)
  - Voting miscellaneous (Box 50)
  - Watergate 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Welfare 1964 (Box 50)
  - West Bloomfield Hills Republican Club 1968 (Box 50)
  - Wolverine Boys State 1963 (Box 50)
  - Wolverine State Republican Organization 1969-1971 (Box 50)
- Campaign Files
  Although much of the record group pertains in some way to election campaigns, the series Campaigns is a convenient source of information about the candidates and issues in the state and national elections in the period of 1962 to 1978. The series includes much campaign material and memoranda about issues and strategy.
  - 1948-1960 (Box 50)
  - 1961-1962 (Box 51)
  - 1962-1963 (Box 52)
  - 1964 (Box 53)
  - 1964 (Box 54)
  - 1964-1966 (Box 55)
  - 1966 1968 (Box 56)
  - 1968 (Box 57)
  - 1970 (Box 58)
  - 1970, 1972 (Box 59)
    (includes files from Lenore Romney's 1970 campaign for the U.S. Senate)
  - 1972, 1974 (Box 60)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 61)
  - 1978 (Box 62)
- Convention Files
  The Convention series has files on the administration, platform, and procedures of the state conventions and on the participation of the state delegation to the Republican National Convention.
  - National Convention
    - Pre-1960 (Box 62)
    - 1960 (Box 62)
    - 1964 (Box 62)
    - 1968 (Box 63)
    - 1972 (Box 63)
    - 1976 (Box 63)
    - 1976 (Box 64)
  - State Conventions
    - Undated and 1964 (Box 64)
    - 1964-1967 (Box 65)
    - 1968-1972, 1975 (Box 66)
- Miscellaneous
  The Miscellaneous series includes files of background information compiled on various individuals prior to their appointment to various state boards and commissions. Similar files will be found in the papers of individual Michigan governors also housed at the library.
  - Patronage files (Box 67)
  - Miscellaneous unprocessed (Box 68)
- Sound recordings
  Sound recordings consists of reel-to-reel tapes of Republican events such as state conventions.
  [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
  - Republican State Convention, 1966 August 27, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-3-1]; mp3 file; (Michigan Republican State Convention in Detroit. Speeches by Gerald Ford and Bob Griffin. Includes voting and precedures for the convention.)
    - [Part 2], [85816-SR-3-2]; mp3 file; (Michigan Republican State Convention in Detroit. Speeches by Gerald Ford and Bob Griffin. Includes voting and precedures for the convention.)
  - Republican State Convention, 1966 August 27, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-4-1]; mp3 file; (Michigan Republican State Convention in Detroit. Begins with a nominating speech by Trudy Huebner. Includes speeches, voting, and precedures. )
  - George Romney before GOP Leadership Meeting, Detroit, 1967 November 18, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-6-1]; mp3 file; (Romney remarks on Open Housing and Human Dignity.)
  - Michigan Republican Seminar on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1968 January 19, 20, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-7-1]; mp3 file; (Unexpected content; commercial tape of Herb Albert's Tijuana Brass Band Vol. 2, no other content.)
    - [Part 2], [85816-SR-7-2]; mp3 file; (Unexpected content; commercial tape of Herb Albert's Tijuana Brass Band Vol. 2, no other content.)
  - Michigan Republican Seminar on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1968 January 19, 20, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-8-1-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 3, Parts 5 and 6. Ten separate announcements discussing political platforms ranging from the Michigan Constitution, taxes, and highway building and funding.)
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-8-1-2]; mp3 file; (Unknown speakers discussing juvenile detention centers.)
    - [Part 2], [85816-SR-8-2]; mp3 file; ("Face Michigan" Radio program, hosted by Fred Douglas interviewing James Hare, then Michigan Secretary of State.)
  - Michigan Republican Seminar on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1968 January 19, 20, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-9-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 4; Parts 7 and 8. Includes speech from Congressman Jim Harvey. Governor Milliken in attendance)
    - [Part 2], [85816-SR-9-2]; mp3 file; (Tape is very quiet. Discussing metropolitan problems and their effects on taxes and society.)
  - Michigan Republican Seminar on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1968 January 19, 20, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-10-1]; mp3 file; (Miscellaneous speeches discussing politics. Tape is very quiet and speakers are unidentified.)
    - [Part 2], [85816-SR-10-2]; mp3 file; (Speech by James Goetz by Lieutenant Governor of Minnesota. References Governor William Milliken and others.)
  - Michigan Republican Seminar on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1968 January 19, 20, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-11-1]; mp3 file; (Various speeches discussing metropolitan problems in the United States. )
    - [Part 2], [85816-SR-11-2]; mp3 file; (Includes speech from Congressman Jim Harvey. Governor Milliken in attendance. Content is identical to 85816-SR-9-1.)
  - Michigan Republican Seminar on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1968 January 19, 20, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-12-1]; mp3 file; (Seminar, Dr. Wright. Various speakers discussing racial relations in metropolitan areas.)
    - [Part 2], [85816-SR-12-2]; mp3 file; (Seminar, Dr. Wright. Various speakers discussing racial relations in metropolitan areas.)
  - 8th Biennial Mackinac Leader Conference, Saturday Brunch Honoring Michigan Congressmen, 1968 September 14-16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-13-1]; mp3 file; (Al Sederberg, leader of the Titanic Ten, and others give speeches.)
  - 8th Biennial Mackinac Leader Conference, Saturday Dinner, 1968 September 14-16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-14-1]; mp3 file; (Gift raffle at Saturday Dinner and recording of dinner.)
  - 8th Biennial Mackinac Leader Conference, Sunday Brunch, 1968 September 14-16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-15-1]; mp3 file; (Concluding session at the Grand Hotel. Includes invocation and speeches and addresses wrapping up conference.)
  - 8th Biennial Mackinac Leader Conference, Reform Revision; McLaughlin; Bush; Ray, 1968 September 14-16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Part 1], [85816-SR-16-1]; mp3 file; (Appears to be three segments spliced together. Various speeches discussing the role of the Republican party and issues relevant to the party's platform.)
  - Republican State Convention, 1972 September 2, 5 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
    - [Tape 1, Part 1], [85816-SR-17-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; Voting and precedures as part of the 1972 State Republic Convention.)
    - [Tape 2, Part 1], [85816-SR-18-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; Voting and precedures as part of the 1972 State Republic Convention.)
    - [Tape 3, Part 1], [85816-SR-19-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3; Voting and precedures as part of the 1972 State Republic Convention.)
    - [Tape 4, Part 1], [85816-SR-20-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 4; Voting and precedures as part of the 1972 State Republic Convention.)
    - [Tape 5, Part 1], [85816-SR-21-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 5; Voting and precedures as part of the 1972 State Republic Convention.)
- Photographs
  Photographs in the SCC records are primarily portraits of candidates for state office, although there are some campaign views and a Detroit polling place where there was a question of voter fraud.
  - Individuals [primarily portraits; complete listing of names available in collection]
    - A-Z, 38 folders
      (include individual photos for)
      - Ahren, Don E. (Box 71)
      - Allen, Glenn S. [1964 campaign] (Box 71)
      - Allen, Don E. (Box 71)
      - Allen, Lester (Box 71)
      - Allen, Richard (Box 71)
      - Anderson, Loren D. [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Andrus, Clifford A. (Box 71)
      - Anspach, Charles L. (Box 71)
      - Arnett, Homer (Box 71)
      - Augenstein, Leroy G. (Box 71)
      - Auenstein, Merle R. (Box 71)
      - Axe, John R. (Box 71)
      - Backus, Mrs. Ross (Jean) (Box 71)
      - Baker, Deane (Box 71)
      - Baker, Raymond S. (Box 71)
      - Balden, Al (Box 71)
      - Ballenger, William [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Balzhiser, Richard E. (Box 71)
      - Banks, William V. (Box 71)
      - Bashara, G. (Box 71)
      - Beach, Robert (Box 71)
      - Beadle, Frank J. (Box 71)
      - Beauregard, Eugene (Box 71)
      - Beebe, N. Lorraine (Box 71)
      - Bell, Joseph (Box 71)
      - Bishop, Donald (Box 71)
      - Blackwell, Robert (Box 71)
      - Bohn, Walter (Box 71)
      - Bolt, Andrew (Box 71)
      - Bousma, Oscar E. (Box 71)
      - Boyer, Mrs. -- [with Helen Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Breakey, James, Jr. (Box 71)
      - Breckley, James H. (Box 71)
      - Breeden, Robert V. (Box 71)
      - Brennan, Bert C. (Box 71)
      - Brennan, Thomas E. (Box 71)
      - Bridgman, Dan [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Briggs, Walter Owen (Box 71)
      - Broomfield, William S. (Box 71)
      - Brown, Garry, III (Box 71)
      - Brown, Jim (Box 71)
      - Brown, Robert J. (Box 71)
      - Brown, Stanley M. (Box 71)
      - Brown, Thomas, L. (Box 71)
      - Broomfield, William R. (Box 71)
      - Brunner, Mrs. Dale (Box 71)
      - Burdick, Benjamin D. (Box 71)